Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 6, Folder (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Executive Development in the Small Company, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Louis A. Allen. From Address on Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Critical Appraisal of Executive Development Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By R. Carter Wellford. From Address on Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: How Do Pepole Grow in a Business organization?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Moorhead Wright. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Work Plan for Training Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Ford Motor Company. Two work plans stapled together, one for the College Graduate Training Program and one for the Co-operative Training Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Building a Better Team Through Personnel Development, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Canada Post Office Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Characteristics of Executive Development Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By F. Paul Bunker. Special Studies No. 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Staff Training Course 1957, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Canadian National Railways. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Job Rotation: A Study and Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By James Morris. From Occasional Papers in Management - Organization - Industrial Relations No. 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Management Development (What it is - how to understand it - how to make it work for you), Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Clare Fraser. Paper presented to the Engineering Institute of Canada on April 10, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: An Analysis of Twelve University Executive Development Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Jon R. Ivarson; Earl G. Planty. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Report of Nordenswan's Period of Observation in the United States August 29, 1956 - April 1, 1957, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Lars Gustaf Nordenswan. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: University Education for the Business in the U.S.A, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Norman C. Hunt. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Objectives for Management Training, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Walter A. Thompson. From The Business Quarterly Vol. XXIII, No. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Guide for In-Service Instructor Training Naval Officers Schools, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Navy, Bureau of Naval Personnel. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: How to Improve Executive Training, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Lyndall F. Urwick. Interview with Nation's Business. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Lessons Learned from Executive Development Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Management Intern Programs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Civil Service Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Action Program of the Council for International Progress in Management (USA), Inc., Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Council for International Progress in Management (USA), Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Management In an Era of Dynamic Technology, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Massachusetts Institute of Technology, School of Industrial Management. Collection of papers delivreed at Executive Development Convocations. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: New Directions in Liberal Education for Executives, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By Peter E. Siegle. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Management Development: A Systematic Approach to the Provision of Supervisors and Managers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    By F. I. de la P. Garforth. Item is in English.
- Box 6, Folder (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Strengthening the Management Team, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Thomas A. Mahoney; Roberta J. Nelson. From "Business News Notes" No. 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Humanistic Education for Business Executives, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Morse Peckham. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Ordnance Management Engineering Training Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of the Army. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Training Facilities in the Field of Human Relations: Report on the United Kingdom, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By S. D. M. King. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Formation Dans Le Domaine Des Relations Humaines: Rapport Sur L'Italie, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By V. M. Clarke. Item is in French.
  - Item 6: Training Facilities in the Field of Human Relations: Report on Germany, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By V. M. Clarke. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Training Director's Job in the Development of Men, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Industrial Training Council of New York. From a conference on June 14-15, 1955; Contains conference notes, source material, and the final report bound together. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Digest of Air Force Executive Development Institute, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Air Force. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Management Development Methods, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By William F. Wrightnour. From "Address on Industrial Relations". Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Aiming for the Top, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By William B. Given, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Executive Development in Action: Patterns and Techniques, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Raymond L. Randall. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Recruitment and Training of Men Intended for Management Positions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: The Selection, Training, and Development of Tomorrow's Executives, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Gaylord A. Freeman, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Principles of Business Management, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By H. W. Prentis, Jr. Address before the Wholesale Distributors of the Armstrong Line on December 14, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: General Electric's Philosophy and Approach to Manager Development, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Marc deFarranti. Remarks to the Annual Management Conference on May 19, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Education for Business Leadership: The Role of the German "Hochschulen", Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Heinz Hartmann. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Top Management and Its Development, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By Princeton University. Bibliography from Selected References No. 67. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Teaching Guide for AFL-CIO Stewards, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A Teaching Guide for AFL-CIO Stewards, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Mutal Challenge of Library Services to Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By American Library Association. From "Library Service to Labor" Vol. 9, No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Union Training Program of the AFL Paper Unions, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By George W. Brooks; Russell Allen. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Training The World's Trade Unionists, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Shop Steward, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Max Swerdlow. Comic book/script-like pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Shop Steward: Key to a Strong Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Learning Process With Applications to Workers' Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Milton M. Schwartz; Irvine L. H. Kerrison. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Steward Training in CIO Unions, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Mildred Bersh. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Thirteen Years in a Labor School, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Thomas J. Darby. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO Manual for Shop Stewards, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Preparing for a Career in Labor Leadership, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Garmet Workers' Union. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations College, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Paraffine Companies, Inc. News releases reviewing speeches at college sessions, and other material concerning the college; Various newspaper clippings and reports bound together. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Harvard Trade Union Fellowship Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report on the Trade Union Fellowship Project at Harvard 1942-43, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Harvard University. Correspondence to John W. Riegel attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Fellowships for Trade Union Leaders, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Yale University. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Re Proposals for Establishing a Labor Extension Service in the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Statement submitted to the House Committee on Education and Labor in Connection. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Eduation Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Pennsylvania State College. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Manual for Union Stewards and Committeemen, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By University of Michigan, Bureau of Industrial Relations. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Teaching Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Alice Hanson. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Summary of Discussion and Conclusions from Workers' Education Conference, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Union Leadership and Administration Instructor's Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By University of Chicago, Industrial Relations Center. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Preparations for Negotiations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By University of Illinois, Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations. Summary of conference for United Auto Workers - AFL held on January 4-5, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor Education Course Outline Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Training the Foreman and the Shop Steward to Administer the Union Contract, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Bibliography; from "Selected References" No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Preparing a Steward's Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Labor Eduation in Universities, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Caroline F. Ware. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: How to Run a Union Meeting, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By AFL. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Education Discovers Organized Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Labour Goes to College, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By G. A. McAllister. Torn from "Food for Thought" Vol 5., No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Education for Labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Hundreds of Jobs, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By UAW-CIO. A guide to the responsibilities and duties of a president of a UAW-CIO local union. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Shop Steward's Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Barbara Briggs. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Shop Steward's Manual, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Governance and Collective Bargaining in Four-Year Instiutions 1970-1977, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Dan L. Adler. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Discrimination Issues in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Carolyn I. Polowy. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Understanding and Managing Changes in University Labor Relations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Dallas M. Young. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hard Times, Values, and Academic Unions, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Robert M. Nielsen; Irwin H. Polishook. Newspaper stapled inside booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Collective Bargaining in Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Catherine R. Dobson. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Address on Equity and Collective Bargaining in Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Myron Leiberman. From "Government Employee Relation Report" No. 699. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Collective Negotiations in Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Michael Dudra. Symposium on November 8, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Academic Unions, Values, and Democracy, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Productivity in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Public Productivity Review. "Public Productivity Review" Vol. 2, No. 5 special issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Unionization on the College Campus, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Journal of College and University Law. Collection of reports. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Handling Minority Problems in the Shop and in the Union, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Improving Attitudes through Management Leadership, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By James N. Farr. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Study of Attitudes to Factory Work, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By S. Wyatt; R. Marriott. Medical Research Council special report series No. 292. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Assessing Organization Performance with Behavioral Measurments, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Stanley E. Seashore. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What Employees Say About Management's Leadership, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Opinion Research Corporation. A report of The Public Opinion Index for Industry Vol 12, No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Motivations: Why People Buy, Why They Work, How to Deal With Them, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Business Week. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Interest in Company Success - How Can It Be Stimulated and Maintained?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By John W. Riegel. From "Address on Industrial Relations". Item is in English.
  - Item 6: You Said It!, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Landers, Frary & Clark. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: National Supervisory Opinion Survey on What Supervisors Think About Problems Ahead, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Management Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employees' Attitudes Toward Unionization, Management, and Factory Conditions: A Survey Case Study, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    By Anthony Stampolis. Research Paper Series No. 7. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 232 Institutions, with 342 Campuses, that have Collective Bargaining Agents, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Edward P. Kelley, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Some Suggested Advantages and Disadvantages of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special Report #1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Postsecondary Public Employment Legislation, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Thomas Emmet. Special Report #2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Postsecondary Public Employment Legislation Revised Status Report - August 1974, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Thomas Emmet. Special report #4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Faculty Governance and Collective Bargaining: An Early Appraisal, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By James P. Begin. Special report #5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Developing Trends in Content of Collective Bargaining Contracts in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By John Andes. Special report #6. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Albion College Votes "No Agent": A Case Study, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Virginia Lee Lussier. Special report #7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: National Faculty Associations in Collective Bargaining: A Comparative Discussion, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Virginia Lee Lussier. Special report #8. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The "No Agent" Vote at NYU: A Conside Legal History, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Gerald A. Bodner. Special Report #9. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Faculty Grievances at SUNY: The First Two Years Under a Negotiated Contract, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Ronald P. Satryb. Special report #10. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Some Primary Concerns Expresed By Campus Administrators, Trustees, Faculty, Students, Unions and Taxpayers About Collective Bargaining Laws, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #11. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: 243 Institutions, With 357 Campuses, That Have Collective Bargaining Agents, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Edward P. Kelley, Jr. Special report #12. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Unionization of Professors at the University of Delaware, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Robert L. Sawicki. Special report #13. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Suggested Inclusions in State Legislations for higher Eduation Institutions Which Wish to Name the Board of Governors as Employer, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #14. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Suggested Inclusions in State Legislation for Higher Education Institutions Which Wish to Name the Chief Executive Officer as Employer, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #13. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Collective Bargaining: Its Effects on Campus Governance, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Michael A. Falcons. Special report #16. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Analysis of Legislation in 23 States Enabling Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #17; May 1976 update attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Resources for Shaping Collective Bargaining Laws to Meet the Special Needs of Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #18; June 1978 attached to front. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Prospective Issues at the Academic Collective Bargaining Table, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Thomas Mannix. Special report #19. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Academic Judgment and Grievance Arbitration in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Harold Levy. Special report #20. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: 1975 Legislative Activity Progress Report on Postsecondary Collective Negotiations Bills, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Thomas A. Emmet. Special Report #21. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Current Status of College Students in Academic Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Alan Shark. Special report #22. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Application of Non-Discrimination Law and Regulations to Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #23. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Faculty Collective Bargaining and Academic Decision Making, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Joseph J. Orze. Special report #24. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Scope of Public Sector Bargaining in 14 Selected States, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service. Special report #25. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Preparation of Faculty Representation Cases -- A Checklist of Issues for Private Colleges and Universities, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Arthur P. Menard; Nicholas DiGiovanni. Special report #26. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: The Art of Settling Grievances: A Study in Campus Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Ronald P. Satryb. Special report #27. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: State Legislation and the Status of Collective Bargaining in Community and Junior Colleges, 1976, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Joseph N. Hankin. Special report #28. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Management Prerogatives and Faculty Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By George W. Angell. Special report #29. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: From Impasse to "Lockout": Community College of Beaver County, September 1976, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Janet Novotny Bacon. Special report #30. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Is Institutional Prestige the Key Variable In Faculty Collective Bargaining?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Margaret K. Chandler; Daniel Julius; Thomas Mannix. Special report #31. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The Appropriateness of Collective Bargaining Between Educational Institutions and Their "Student/Employees": A Legal Analysis, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Gerald A. Bodner. Special report #32. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: The National Labor Relations Board in Higher Education, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Peter D. Walther. Special report #33. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Conflict Resolution in Academe: Prevent or Settle Early, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Joseph K. Orze. Special report #34. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Bargaining Unit Placement of Religious Faculty, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Edward P. Kelley, Jr.; Frank C. Gerry. Special report #35. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Trends and Patterns of Change in Public Community College Collective Bargaining Contracts, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Robert H. Kellett. Reseach Summar #1. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Impact of Collective Bargaining on Conflict Resolution Practices, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By David W. Leslie. Research Summary #2. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Faculty, Student and Staff Attitudes Toward Potential Collective Bargaining Issues at The Ohio State University, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Daniel J. Phelan. Research summary #3. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: An Analysis of some Aspects of Social Conflict at Henry Ford Community College (1963-1973), Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Ray A. Howe. Research summary #4. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Should Non-Teaching Professional Be Included in a Faculty Union?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By Robert H. Kellett. Research summary #5. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Grievance Arbitration in Higher Education: Recent Experiences with Arbitration of Faculty Status Disputes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    By June Miller Weisberger. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Summary Report of Conference on Union Health and Welfare Funds, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    By Automobile Manufacturers Association. Speech "Welfare Funds in Collective Bargaining" by Theodore R. Iserman is attached as an appendix. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Close-Up of Closures, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    By Alfred Lief. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Proceedings of Conferences on Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    By University of Michigan, Bureau of Industrial Relations. Conference held on June 6-7, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Survey Report of Private Employee Benefits in Distribution, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Determining Employee Attitudes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    By Norman S. Fregger. Industrial Commentaries Vol. 1 No.1. Item is in English.
- Box 7, Folder (Box 7, Folder 11)